landofcoder.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy - Landofcoder

All of information you provide through this website, we don't sell or distribute to third parties except that it is legally required. All user information are gathered to serve your needs and reply your request.

All personal information that are used to identify any individual such as a first and last name, home address, email address or other contact information keep in secret. As usual you can visit our web page without telling who you are or revealing any personal info about yourselfWe use personal information to process and deliver your order for bill. Maybe it is used to provide a more pleasant shopping experience

As you may know that, when you browse our website, it automatically places all data file called"cookies" on your computer. The data will help to identify you if you visit multiple pages on oursite at the same session. Hence we don't need to ask you for password on each page. Onceyou close the browser or logout, this cookie is no longer in effectIf you want to disable cookies, these benefits will be impacted

We guarantee that your personal information is protected. We store your info in secured server.Moreover, SSL is used for checkout process to keep your billing info safe. No credit card info issaved on our system. We don’t share your personal information with any other third parties.

Please notice that the privacy policy maybe change in the future. When there is any changes wewill post it on this page or if the changes is important we will show you notification.If you have any question, please feel free to contact us
